kissflow.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy |

#### General

At OrangeScape, we respect our customers and users need for online privacy and protect any personal information that may be shared with us, in an appropriate manner. Our practice as regards use of your personal information is as set forth below in this Privacy Policy Statement. As a condition to use of OrangeScape Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.

#### Information we collect

We collect information in two ways:

**Information you give us.  **We collect information from google apps to provide better services to all our users – that includes first name, last name, email id and email group(s) each user belong to. This information is synchronized on a periodic basis and if the user is deleted or made inactive in google apps domain, we delete or deactivate the user in our application as well.  We do not collect passwords or store documents in our application.

**Information we get from your use of our services.**  Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you visit the application or when you used a specific feature. Our logging system automatically collects information like the internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, features accessed, errors generated, time zone, operating system information and other such information that is transmitted in the header of the user’s HTTP request and stores in log files. We use these log files to analyze trends, administer and improve the application. We don’t collect or store application or user specific data as part of logs.

#### How we use information we collect

We use the information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authorization, services improvement, and research. When you contact OrangeScape, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing.

#### How secure is your information

We adopt industry appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data stored in your user account. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees who need to know such information in connection with providing OrangeScape Services to you and are bound by confidentiality obligations.

Orangescape does not sell the personally identifiable information you provide for financial gain nor does OrangeScape share such information with third parties for the purpose of sending you advertisements for products or services unaffiliated with OrangeScape or with its affiliates or business partners.

#### Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.  

#### Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a explicit email notification to all users who hold “admin” role in our service .

Last Updated: 12th December, 2012
